freesitemapxml.com 2014-05-15

# Free Sitemap XML

## Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the Free Sitemap XML treatment of personal information that is recorded when you create a sitemap through our free service.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the Free Sitemap XML website, nor does it extend to people that Free Sitemap XML does not employ or manage.

### Information Collection and Use

Unlike many sitemap generators that charge for sitemap creation and collect personal information as well, Free Sitemap XML is a free service. The only information collected during sitemap creation is Name, Email Address, URL, and IP Address.

Your use of Free Sitemap XML's sitemap generator constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a business service for your website(s). In exchange, Free Sitemap XML reserves the right to use the contact information collected during sign-up to provide our free newsletter, to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to inform you of additions to the GreenWave Online Network of websites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

With the exception of autoresponse messages which are sent when your sitemap is created and contain important sitemap results, you may remove yourself from all newsletters, notices or announcements using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact: inquiry[at]freesitemapxml.com. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours.

### Cookies

At this time, cookies are not used on the Free Sitemap XML site.

### Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to Free Sitemap XML staff.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Free Sitemap XML may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

### Questions or Suggestions

Questions or suggestions may be sent to: inquiry[at]freesitemapxml.com
